现在，让我们把很多东西拼凑起来。
Now let's bring a lot of pieces together.
精心设计的抽象数据的巨大优势
An enormous advantage of a well-designed abstract data
类型是它封装并强制执行属性
type is that it encapsulates and enforces properties
否则我们必须在一个先决条件中加以规定。
that we would otherwise have to stipulate in a precondition.
例如，不是像这样的规范
For example, instead of a spec like this
它的前提条件是
with its elaborate precondition that says it's set
1是一个字符串，是一个排序集
1, which is a string, is a sorted set
没有重复的字符。
of characters with no repeats.
第二组也是。
Set 2 is likewise.
它再次按顺序返回一组字符
And it returns, again, a set of characters in sorted order
没有重复。
with no repeats.
我们可以使用一个ADT来捕获
We can instead use an ADT that captures
所需的属性，排序集
that desired property, sorted set
人物，上面写着。
characters, which says this.
这更容易理解，因为ADT的名称
This is easier to understand because the name of the ADT
排序而不是字符表示所有
sort instead of character conveys all
程序员需要知道。
the programmer needs to know.
它也更安全，因为Java静态检查
It's also safer from bugs because Java static checking
开始发挥作用。
comes into play.
以及不重复排序的所需条件
And the required conditions sorted with no repeats
可以在一个地方强制执行，即排序集类型。
can be enforced in exactly one place, the sorted set type.
很多地方我们可能使用了先决条件
Many of the places where we might have used preconditions
关于你在课程中看到的问题集或早期代码
on problem sets or earlier code you've seen in the course
如果有一个自定义的抽象数据类型
would have benefited from having a custom abstract data type
相反。
instead.